cloudcc.com 2018-08-02

# CloudCC Privacy Policy

CloudCC respects your need for online privacy and protects any Personal Information that you may share with us.Our practice with respect to use of your Personal Information is as set forth below in this Privacy Policy Statement. As a condition to use CloudCC , you consent to the terms of the Privacy Policy Statement as it may be updated from time to time. 

#### Scope of this Privacy Policy 

**·** During the Registration Process for creating a user account, we request for your personal information, such as your name and email address.

**·** Your usage details such as time, frequency, duration and pattern of use, features used, IP address, system language and the amount of storage used will be recorded by us in order to enhance your experience of CloudCC and to help us provide you the best possible service.

**·** We will legally obtain users’ personal information from business partners.You understand and agree that the following information IS NOT applicable to this Privacy Policy.

**·** The key words you entered when using search service provided by CloudCC.

**·** We will collect the information you released at CloudCC.

**·** Violation of laws, regulations and CloudCC rules.

**·** Measures taken against you.  

* * *

#### Information Use 

**·** We should not share your personal information with anyone for promotional purposes, nor do we utilize it for any purposes not expressly consented to by you.

**·** If a third part (including the company associated with CloudCC) services you alone or CloudCC services you with a third part, after the end of the service, the third part will be prevented from accessing all user information even they previously had access to.

**·** CloudCC may provide you with information and services based on your personal information and interests, including but not limited to sending you our product and service information.

* * *

#### Information Disclosure 

We will disclose all or part of your information as you wish or as required by law under the following circumstances:

**·** With your consent and permission, disclose your information to a third party.

**·** In order to provide the products and services you required, CloudCC must share your information with a third party.

**·** CloudCC will disclose your information to a third party, an administrative or judicial authority in accordance with the relevant legal provisions or at the request of an administrative or judicial body.

**·** If you violate laws and regulations on CloudCC agreement and regulations, you need to disclose your information to a third party.

**·** If you are an intellectual property complainant and have filed a complaint, CloudCC will disclose your information to the respondent at the request of the respondent so that both parties can resolve the rights dispute.

**·** In a transaction created by the CloudCC, if either party to the transaction fulfils or partially fulfils the transaction obligation and makes a request for information disclosure, CloudCC has the right to decide to provide the user with the necessary information, such as phone of the other party to the transaction, to facilitate the completion of the transaction or the resolution of the dispute.

**·** According to laws, regulations or policies, CloudCC considers it appropriate to disclose.  

* * *

#### Information Storage and Exchange 

Your information and data CloudCC collected will be stored in the CloudCC and/or associated company server, and may be accessed, stored and displayed in your country, region, or outside of the location where the information and data were collected.  
If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy Statement or associated practices, please contact us.
